The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Knight of the Ribbon,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Fiftieth Episode
The Fortune Teller
- Look. What is that over there?
- It's appearing out of nowhere!
It's a type of tower
that we've never seen before.
What a strange construction.
What could it mean?
It's truly imposing.
It appeared so suddenly...
- I think it's the work of magic.
- I think so too!
Listen, Sire!
We've discovered what the tower is!
It's an enormous Fortress
that Union X...
...is building
on the territory of Goldland!
- A Union X Fortress?!
- Good heavens!
- My goodness, Union X!
- Something terrible is going to happen!
If that is the
case, I fear it too!
I understand! X intends
to occupy our Kingdom...
...using the tower!
- It could be!
It would be terrible! Union
X is capable of even that!
- Oh, my God!
- Now I would like to know if the tower...
...has already been completed.
- No, our observations...
...show that the work
is still in progress, Sire!
We must strengthen the defenses before
they complete the construction.
I believe that tower
will decide the fate of Silverland!
Damn Union X! I won't give you
my country without a fight!
In Silverland
they are preparing defenses
All this fussing
won't do them any good!
When our tower is
completed, it will be over for them!
- How much longer to finish the work?
- We are doing...
...as fast as possible,
as you can see for yourself, boss!
Come on! Move it!
Faster!
I asked when
the work will be completed!
We don't have enough slaves,
so it will take more time
than expected!
You don't have enough slaves?
And why don't you get more?
But boss...
there are no more!
We are using
all the slaves from Goldland!
Did you say "slaves from Goldland"?
In front of us is Silverland.
We will kidnap a hundred
of its inhabitants...
...and we will force them
to work for us!
Look at them struggling in vain!
This is how Union X does
things! Go to Silverland!
Look! Millions of birds
are darkening the sun!
You say that citizens
have disappeared?
Exactly, Princess!
A hundred people...
...were enveloped by a
swarm of birds and vanished!
Did you see where
those birds came from?
No, but it is rumored that they cover...
...an enormous giant
clad in iron armor!
I heard it said that the iron
giant is an evil spirit!
They say that birds
will fill Silverland...
...and that we will all be devoured
by the evil spirit!
Don't be foolish!
I haven't been drinking! I assure you
that it's all true!
Someone who never drinks
told me so!
He said he saw a giant
clad in black armor,
crossing the sky
on a black horse!
Who's there?
People, how about
having your fortunes told?
You ugly old hag,
stay away from me!
I don't believe in divination.
Go away!
There are bad omens
over your heads!
Soon you will see
the black birds arriving!
Be careful and don't
panic. It's no use!
My omens
have never been wrong!
Go away!
Remember my words!
I am never wrong!
Did you hear that jinx?
Better go home, Tink!
What will you do if that giant
actually appears?
And what will you do, Sapphire?
I will fight! I will try to stop
him and save the Kingdom!
Then I will fight with you too!
But you are too small! At this
hour you should already be at home!
I thought I saw something
pass under the bridge!
Wait, I'm going to see!
Hey! Sapphire, what are you doing? Wait!
It's not fair! Why are you leaving
me here? Take me with you!
Listen, I'm not afraid of just
any shadow! Anyway, I know...
Three more monsters!
- What happened to him?
- He must be crazy!
Did you see?
Look! This is the cat
that was with the fortune teller before!
I recognize it!
Go away, you nasty cat!
Look, a flock of birds.
The fortune teller was right.
Let's run, quick!
Hey, listen!
I think I hear something!
It sounds like horse hooves!
Help!
The ghost giant is coming!
What is it?
Damn, so many birds!
This is the largest flock
I have ever seen!
Where are you, ghost giant?
Come out!
Opale, you stay here and don't move,
I'm counting on you!
Come out, ghost giant,
accept a challenge from me!
Come explain to me why
you kidnap the men of Silverland!
Damn, it's huge!
I won't allow you to enter
my country, ghost giant!
Before I lose, I will resist
with all my strength!
It's gone!
The ghost giant has disappeared!
I can't breathe anymore!
Sapphire, regain consciousness!
Please, my daughter!
Thank goodness Opal caught her
and brought her back here,
otherwise she would have died!
I'm so worried about her..
What did the doctor say?
He said he doesn't have
a sure remedy,
because he has never seen
a poison like this in this country!
Poor Sapphire!
How I wish I were in her place!
Sapphire, wake up, please!
Your Majesty,
hoping to please you,
I thought of bringing you a fortune teller!
You'll see that she will be
of some help to Sapphire as well!
What do you think a fortune
teller can do for Sapphire?
She will be able to see
good or bad omens...
...in the Princess's destiny!
Come!
You're all here, good! Good!
Then I can begin!
How frightening!
I'm sorry for her!
This castle will be surrounded by a
thick black mist tomorrow evening!
You will hear a sound
coming from inside this mist.
A huge giant will arrive!
And what will become of Sapphire? Tell us!
The ghost giant will kidnap her!
No one will be able to prevent it,
because if you resist,
there will be no escape for you!
- Oh, good heavens, it's terrible!
- You will be annihilated!
Did you hear? No one must be
in the path of the phantom giant!
What a cruel fate! She will fall into the
hands of the giant while she sleeps!
There is no way to prevent it!
- My Sapphire...
- Quiet!
We must keep it a secret that
Sapphire is no longer in this room.
A secret, you say?
And you want no one to notice..
..that she is no longer in there?
- Look!
I will take Sapphire's place!
- But you cannot do that, Your Majesty!
- I tried to dissuade her,
but I didn't succeed!
That's why I sent for you!
Then, if there is no other solution,
I will challenge the giant! I am ready!
No, wait! It's better if you go
to X's castle, do you understand, Franz?
It is said that the giant is moved
by a spirit from the castle.
Perhaps the black mist will disappear
if that is destroyed!
You can count on me, Queen! I
will tear down that damned castle!
Sapphire, I will do
everything to protect you.
For you I would even
cross the gates of hell!
Wait for me with confidence and
just continue your sleep. I will win!
Goodbye, Your Majesty!
Be careful, Franz!
I wish you with all my heart
to succeed in this endeavor!
Oh, it's already night!
- Help! Let's run!
- Let's run!
What are these screams?
The ghost giant the
fortune-teller spoke of!
No one has noticed my presence!
Come on, crows,
rise into the night sky!
- Oh, Sapphire, you've recovered!
- What happened to me?
Where am I? But this...
This is mother's room!
- There's a reason why you're here!
- What?!
Mother, where are
you? Mother! Mother!
The ghost giant kidnapped her
just like the fortune teller said!
- The ghost giant?
- You shouldn't have gotten up!
You're still too weak!
You've been sick, you know?
I must find the
strength to fight!
- But you're still recovering!
- Damn X! Give me back my mother!
See? I told you that you
haven't recovered yet!
But you are the mysterious
knight and no longer Sapphire!
Of course, Tink! I appeared
because I have a task to perform.
Come, Tink!
Damn X! I will succeed in taking
my mother from your clutches!
There are only two guards.
- Help, I can't see anything!
- Me neither! Help! Help!
Your Excellency, here
is what I promised you!
Well done!
You've done a good job.
Now we have nothing to fear!
- There's Sapphire!
- Damn! What an idiot you are!
- This is the Queen of Silverland!
- Death and damnation! Indeed!
This clever one was lying on the bed
instead of her daughter!
- The bells are ringing!
- Alarm! There are enemies!
Prince Franz!
Drop your swords,
citizens of Goldland!
Return to the prisons, slaves,
or the Queen will be killed!
Prince Franz!
Throw your sword to the ground!
Or do you not care...
...about what might happen
to the Queen of the neighboring country?
It is unfair of you
to take a hostage!
I will count to ten!
One!
What's happening?
But that's my mother!
Three, four.
Six!
Nine!
- Franz, don't worry about me.
- Ten!
Wait, we surrender!
You're a good Prince!
Now kill him,
so that he may be an example
for the others!
- The mysterious knight!
- What?!
- Take this!
- Get lost, you brat!
- Careful, Tink!
- A little brat like you certainly won't beat me!
Come on!
Damn, you're sharp!
Go to hell!
- Dammit!
- Franz, take this!
Thanks!
And now, it’s our turn!
Damn, I didn't expect that!
- For now, it's better to retreat!
- Wait, X!
You royal pain in the ass, you'll
vanish along with the tower!
Dammit! Where did he go?
I can't see him!
- Franz, are you alright?
- Yes, I'm fine, but X has disappeared!
Watch out! Let's get out of here, Franz!
The tower is collapsing!
It's collapsing!
Everyone escape, quickly!
Quickly, Franz!
X forced our people
to build the tower...
...and he used the crows
to maneuver the giant!
I'm heading to Silverland
at a run!
See you soon, then!
We will follow you shortly. Is that alright?
- Goodbye!
- Franz, if I see Sapphire,
I will give her your regards!
And I'll tell her you'll see each other soon!
Thank you, mysterious knight!
Goodbye and see you soon!
Bye! Bye!
Perhaps you thought
you could defeat me,
but you won't succeed in doing so!
I will never surrender!
Next time will be the one
and I will destroy Silverland!
Of that you can be sure!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP